Guide to the Rice University Controller's Office records, 1908-2008 UA 195
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Controller's Office records, 1908-2008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University. Controller's Office
UA 195
4 Linear Feet (4 boxes)
Official records of the Rice University Office of the Controller 1908 through 2008. Collection equals 4 boxes (4 linear feet).
Historical note
Rice University's Office of the Controller properly records all appropriate financial transactions of the University in a timely manner and designs processes, procedures, and systems to safeguard the University's financial resources. Various areas of the Controller's Office are Benefits Accounting, Cashier's Office, Current Funds, Investment Accounting, Loan Collections, Payments / Disbursements, Payables / Payment Solutions, Payroll, Property Accounting and Research and Cost Accounting. Their administrative partners are Human Resources, Administrative Systems, and the Office of Sponsored Research.
Scope and Contents Note
Official records of the Rice University Office of the Controller, reflecting the results of their daily business in the form of reports.
Conditions Governing Access Note
This material is not open for research without written permission from the Office of the Controller. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Accruals Note
Materials are expected to be added to this collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition Note
Transferred by the Office of the Controller over time and most recently in 2009.
Index Terms
Subjects
Rice University -- History; Universities and colleges
Document Types
financial records
- Series I. Financial reports, 1908-1929, 79842; 1 Linear Feet
  - FIN 1908, 79847 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - FIN 1909, 79848 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - FIN 1910, 79849 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - FIN 1911, 79850 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - FIN 1912, 79851 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - FIN 1913, 79852 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - FIN 1914, 79853 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - FIN 1915, 79854 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - FIN 1916, 79855 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - FIN 1917, 79856 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - FIN 1918, 79857 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - FIN 1919, 79858 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - FIN 1920, 79859 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - FIN 1921, 79860 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - FIN 1922, 79861 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - FIN 1923, 79862 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - FIN 1924, 79863 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - FIN 1925, 79864 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - FIN 1926, 79865 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - FIN 1927, 79866 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - FIN 1928, 79867 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - FIN 1929, 79868 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Series II. Financial reports, 1930-1946; 79843; 1 Linear Feet
  - FIN 1930, 79869 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - FIN 1931, 79870 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - FIN 1932, 79871 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - FIN 1933, 79872 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - FIN 1934, 79873 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - FIN 1935, 79874 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - FIN 1936, 79875 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - FIN 1937, 79876 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - FIN 1938, 79877 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - FIN 1939, 79878 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - FIN 1940, 79879 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - FIN 1941, 79880 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - FIN 1942, 79881 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - FIN 1943, 79882 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - FIN 1944, 79883 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - FIN 1945, 79884 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - FIN 1946, 79885 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Series III. Financial reports, 1947-1962; 79844; 1 Linear Feet
  - FIN 1947, 79886 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - FIN 1948, 79887 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - FIN 1949, 79888 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - FIN 1950, 79889 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - FIN 1951, 1950; 79890 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - FIN 1952, 79891 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - FIN 1953, 79892 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - FIN 1954, 79893 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - FIN 1955, 79894 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - FIN 1956, 79895 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - FIN 1957, 79896 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - FIN 1958, 79897 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - FIN 1959, 79898 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - FIN 1960, 79899 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - FIN 1961, 79900 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - FIN 1962, 79901 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Series IV: Financial reports, 1963-2008; 79845; 1 Linear Feet
  - FIN 1963, 79902 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - FIN 1964, 79903 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - FIN 1965, 79904 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - FIN 1966, 79905 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - FIN 1967, 79906 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - FIN 1968, 79907 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - FIN 1969, 79908 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - FIN 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - FIN 1971, 79910 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - FIN 1972, 79911 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - FIN 1973, 79912 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - FIN 1974, 79913 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - FIN 1975, 79914 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - FIN 1976, 79915 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - FIN 1977, 79916 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - FIN 1978, 79917 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - FIN 1979, 79918 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - FIN 1980, 79919 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - FIN 1981, 79920 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - FIN 1982, 79921 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - FIN 1983, 79922 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - FIN 1984, 79923 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - FIN 1985, 79924 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - FIN 1986, 79925 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - FIN 1987, 79926 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - FIN 1988, 79927 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - FIN 1989, 79928 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - FIN 1990, 79929 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - FIN 1991, 79930 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - FIN 1992, 79931 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - FIN 1993, 79932 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - FIN 1994, 79933 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - FIN 1995, 79934 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - FIN 1996, 79935 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - FIN 1997, 79936 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - FIN 1998, 79937 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - FIN 1999, 79938 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - FIN 2000, 79939 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - FIN 2001, 79940 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - FIN 2002, 79941 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - FIN 2003, 79942 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - FIN 2004, 79943 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - FIN 2005, 79944 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - FIN 2006, 79945 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - FIN 2007, 79946 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - FIN 2008, 79947 (Box 4, Folder 46)